Jimbrows are downloading Ashton Hall. Look up what is coaching program actually include motivational support from Ashton Hall
That's about it. $8,000 please get this telegram app and a database to store your health info now
Give this guard Gancho and prompt to your AI agent of choice and it will create a fucking shitload of tables
Dude create a health chat like this in telegram and let this prompt absolutely rip
We wanted to create a workflow that when you text or send voice messages to telegram
Oh, I ate some pandori chicken dude. I had a very short legs workout
It will send a confirmation and then save it to this messages table
Now we want to run this next prompt which will create a workflow that will look at all of these pending messages
Figure out what you were trying to say whether it was like food or workouts and then write it down in the correct table
Now you can create things like a nutrition coach or even a training coach
Shuttle text you being like, yo, you got to hit the gym dude
This is actually my system by the way, you don't need to pay 8 grand for Ashton Hall to send you motivational quotes
Follow your boy instead. I'll show you how to build cool stuff like this for free